<medium_term_memory>
    <context>
        This is a medium term memory of the AI assistant. It is used to store the general information regarding the closer future. The memory contains 3 defined topics.
    </context>
    <to_do_list>
        - Take a pottery class and create a full tableware set by August (6 months)
        - Read 50 new books across different genres by the end of the year (12 months)
        - Train for and run a 5K race in under 30 minutes by mid-May (4 months)
        - Learn to play guitar well enough to accompany myself singing by my birthday in March (3 months)
        - Cook one new exotic cuisine meal per week for the next 3 months to expand my culinary skills
        - Take beekeeping classes and install my first beehive by spring (6 months)
        - Achieve conversational fluency in Spanish through daily practice over the next year
        - Volunteer 200 hours this year by committing 8 hours every weekend (12 months)
        - Visit 3 new states on a road trip by July (6 months)
        - Create a portfolio website showcasing my photography within 2 months
        - Volunteer to walk shelter dogs twice a week for the next 3 months
        - Master 5 new cocktail recipes per month for the next year
        - Grow an herb garden with 10+ plant varieties by end of summer (6 months)
        - Run 2 half marathons this year - one in spring and one in fall (8 months)
        - Reach intermediate proficiency in French through daily Duolingo lessons by March (4 months)
        - Knit sweaters as holiday gifts for family and friends by November (10 months) 
        - Take improv classes and perform in a live show by December (10 months)
        - Read book on home renovations and remodel my bathroom by May (4 months)
        - Pack picnic and frisbee for beach day with friends tomorrow
        - RSVP for the theater group outing on Sunday
        - Sign up to chaperone the field trip next Thursday
        - Pick up developed photos to make memory scrapbook
        - Schedule times to walk the neighbor's dog while they're on vacation
        - Drop off donations at the homeless shelter downtown
        - Confirm dinner reservations for anniversary date night
        - Buy ingredients to bake cookies for the school bake sale
        - Pick up snacks and refreshments for game night on Friday
        - Don't forget to send the book club meeting invites today
        - Visit the Louvre museum in Paris, the largest art museum in the world.
        - Try the over 200 types of French cheese like Camembert and Brie.
    </to_do_list>
    <goals_with_deadlines>
        - Take a pottery class and create a full tableware set by August (6 months)
        - Read 50 new books across different genres by the end of the year (12 months)
        - Train for and run a 5K race in under 30 minutes by mid-May (4 months)
        - Learn to play guitar well enough to accompany myself singing by my birthday in March (3 months)
        - Cook one new exotic cuisine meal per week for the next 3 months to expand my culinary skills
        - Take beekeeping classes and install my first beehive by spring (6 months)
        - Achieve conversational fluency in Spanish through daily practice over the next year
        - Volunteer 200 hours this year by committing 8 hours every weekend (12 months)
        - Visit 3 new states on a road trip by July (6 months)
        - Create a portfolio website showcasing my photography within 2 months
        - Grow an herb garden with 10+ plant varieties by end of summer (6 months)
        - Reach intermediate proficiency in French through daily Duolingo lessons by March (4 months) 
        - Read book on home renovations and remodel my bathroom by May (4 months)
    </goals_with_deadlines>
    <reminders>
        - Master 5 new cocktail recipes per month for the next year
        - Run 2 half marathons this year - one in spring and one in fall (8 months)
        - Knit sweaters as holiday gifts for family and friends by November (10 months)
        - Take improv classes and perform in a live show by December (10 months)
        - The North Atlantic right whale is an endangered 55 ft whale species needing protection.
        - The Petronas Twin Towers in Malaysia were once the world's tallest buildings.
    </reminders>
</medium_term_memory>